<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoC Guide</string>
    <string name="list">Categories</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="howtoplay">How to play</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="strategies">Strategies</string>
    <string name="news">News</string>
    <string name="morecoolapps">More cool apps</string>
    <string name="aboutdetails">Clash of Clans is a popular iPad/iPhone/iPod/Android game created by \"supercell\". It has been available internationally on the iTunes store for free since its initial v1.7 release on 2 August 2012, and on the Google Play Store since 8 October 2013. From rage-filled Barbarians with glorious mustaches to pyromaniac Wizards, raise your own army and lead your clan to victory! Build your village to fend off raiders, battle against millions of players worldwide, and forge a powerful clan with others to destroy enemy clans.
Clash of Clans is an online multiplayer game in which players build a community (in the form of a clan), train troops, and attack other players to earn gold, elixir and Dark Elixir. Gold and elixir can be used to build defenses that protect the player from other player’s attacks. Elixir and dark elixir is also used to train and upgrade troops and spells. The game also features a pseudo-single player campaign in which the player can attack a series of fortified goblin villages and earn gold and elixir. The game has 2 \'builders\' by default but one can install more builders (maximum 5) using gems, builders are important for upgrading any building. If all builders are busy one has to either wait (if the player wants to upgrade a building) for them to be free or free them up using gem.
To earn and store gold and elixir, players must build gold mines and gold storages and elixir collectors and elixir storages, respectively. Elixir is used to train new troops, carry out research in the laboratory to upgrade troops, to re-load X-Bows (available from Town Hall 9) and to build and upgrade certain buildings, mostly pertaining to buildings used in attacking another player\'s base. Gold is used to build defensive buildings and to upgrade the town hall, which allows access to more buildings and higher levels for existing buildings. At higher levels, dark elixir becomes available; this type of elixir is used to train and upgrade dark elixir troops and heroes, create dark spells, and fuel the Inferno Tower, a defensive building that is available only at Town Hall 10. The Eagle Artillery which is a defensive building that is only available at Town Hall 11, is fueled by elixir. Town Hall 11 also provides access to a new hero - The Grand Warden. It is the only hero born out of elixir. To earn and store dark elixir, players must build dark elixir drills and dark elixir storages.
This app and its content is not affiliated with, endorsed or sponsored by Supercell. For more information see Supercell’s Fan Content Policy: www.supercell.com/fan-content-policy.</string>
    <string name="howtoplaydetails">Clash of Clans is an addictive game where you build a base, protect it, train troops and attack others. As you get more and more gold and elixir resources, your base will get bigger and better! Here is a simple, easy to follow method of how to become an experienced Clash of Clans player.
Get your base up and running. First priority is to make your base more defensive so no one takes away your treasures. Focus on trying to put your town hall in the center of your base so that it is hard to take more trophies from you that come with taking down the town hall.
Go to the Shop, the items to protect your base are under \"Defense.\" Good initial defenses are walls and the mortar. If you have these, you are much less likely to have someone raid you and steal your gold and elixir. Walls are much better upgraded so make sure you can do that quite quickly. Try to get the walls to level 3 as quick as possible.
Since you have limited resources at first, put the walls you buy around the most important buildings only. It is great if you can protect the town hall, gold storage(s) and elixir storage(s). Kick the builder huts and army buildings out. Also, do not try to put walls around everything. It\'s better to have double thick walls than one huge line, right?
Spend your gold, elixir and gems wisely. Do not waste them, especially your gems because they come in short supply. Do not spend your gems! Save them for another builder hut!
Use your gems to build builder\'s huts. It is tempting to them all right away, but don\'t. You will need your gems later.
In the tutorial, you are given 5 wizards to destroy the base. If you only use two, you will have the other 3 in your army camp already. This will let you have wizards at Town Hall 1, which you usually don\'t unlock until later in the game.
The most efficient way to spend gems is to invest in builders\' huts as this enables you to upgrade multiple towers and other defenses at once.
Don\'t spend on extra gold or elixir storage at first, because you don\'t need it.
Remember that defense is the best offense! Build a strong base to protect yourself from attackers. It is very satisfying to have enemies attack you and fail.</string>
    <string name="tipsdetails">Clans are groups of players who join together to support each other, either materially (donating troops) or verbally (giving advice). Players can join clans once they rebuild the special Clan Castle building early on. A major component of the gameplay of Clash of Clans is clans facing off against one another. Clan leaders and co-leaders can begin wars against other clans. Each clan is then given one \"preparation day\" and one \"war day.\" When a player attacks a member of the opposing clan, they receive stars based upon the amount of destruction they cause to the opponent\'s community. Each player is limited to two attacks per war, and the team with the most stars at the end of the war day is declared victorious. If the two clans\' amount of stars are equal, then the victorious clan is the one that has a greater percent destruction. Players receive bonus war loot if he/she use their attacks in the war. This loot is different on different bases and is decided by supercell, the top most base has the most war bonus loot and the last base has the least amount of bonus loot. If the clan wins the war, the bonus loot is fully delivered to the player but during a loss one-third of the loot is delivered to the player. In the May 2016 update, Friendly Challenges were introduced to allow clan-mates to compete amongst other clan-mates, however these challenges do not provide loot or trophies and does not affect a player\'s army.</string>
    <string name="strategiesdetails">Walls are good, but are not the only part in a super awesome base. The #1 mistake I see new players (or not so new players) doing is placing their defenses so they can be targeted by archers spawning outside of the walls. Don\'t make this mistake.
The difference between \'Decent\' and \'Great\' has to do with the way units decide which building to attack next. It is too complicated to get into here (this \'basics\' section) but I think I\'ll cover it later in more detail. The buildings protecting your defenses do matter - Mines/collectors will have more HP than Barracks/Builder\'s Huts.
When you move any building or wall (but not decorations), it shows you white lines one space larger in every direction from that building. This is showing you where enemies can spawn. Make sure you don\'t have any holes in your base to let them spawn inside your walls. That would be bad. I will write about how to leave intentional spawn spots in your base later, in the advanced base defense chapter.
Another common mistake: placing all of your defenses widely spread apart, to cover as many buildings as possible. Dies very easily to several giants. Or to groups of infantry, especially archers. Or to balloons. Which I guess means it just dies to everything.
This often goes along with trying to stuff everything inside your walls, covered later. As a counterpoint to Overlapping Defenses, don\'t try to enclose everything within your walls. First off you will often break Overlapping Defenses and defend your Defenses by trying to cover everything, but secondly it is just a waste of walls. Double thick walls are better than a massive single thick wall.
Absolutely keep your Builder\'s Huts, Laboratory, Barracks, Army Camps and Spell Factory outside your walls. None of these matter if they get destroyed - no progress or resources are lost. Next, I would keep out Gold Mines and Elixir Collectors. Each of these has some consequence if they get attacked: Mines and Collectors can have resources stolen (but only uncollected resources). Some people really like keeping Mines/Collectors inside - It depends on how often you play. If you do keep any inside, make sure they are your highest-level units.
What does that leave? Town Hall, Defenses, Elixir Storage, Gold Storage. All of these should be inside your walls, and as well-protected as possible. If you are at a stage in the game where you don\'t care about trophies, you can also kick your Town Hall outside the walls. You will be easy to defeat, but if you\'re only trying to protect your resources, the Town Hall takes up a lot of space.</string>
    <string name="newsdetails">\"Clash Of Clans\" has a new Dragon event that has reportedly been getting much attention after being announced last month. Based on reports, the new major game promotion is expected to provide some Dragon firepower to the armies.
\"Clash of Clans\" Dragon is among the strongest troops the game has to offer, in terms of strategy. Reports indicate that this is required for taking out defenses and for downing swarms of Goblins and Barbarians that are difficult to reach in the air, and effective as well with a well-timed Rage spell.
Other benefits to the \"Clash of Clans\" discounted Dragons are said to go beyond power, as the troops could be Elixir drains when training, which is an ideal time to stock up on a specific resource while keeping a strong attack. For players who need Elixir, getting involved is needed, Tech Crunch reported.</string>
</resources>
